Guide to the Associate University Librarian for Technical Services, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Associate University Librarian for Technical Services, Yale University, records
1944-2007
RU 215
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
92.75
The records consist of files of Ake Koel, F. Bernice Field, and Donald Waters, including reports and records concerning NELINET, RLG, OCLC, AACR2, library automation, preservation, reclassification, ARL Task Force, catalog continuation, ALA conferences, catalog code revision, union negotiations, and salaries. The records document technical services at the Yale University Library.
Yale University. Library
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 32-B (YRG 32-B), Records of deputy, associate, and assistant librarians of Yale University.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is partially restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of files of Ake Koel, F. Bernice Field, and Donald Waters, including reports and records concerning NELINET, RLG, OCLC, AACR2, library automation, preservation, reclassification, ARL Task Force, catalog continuation, ALA conferences, catalog code revision, union negotiations, and salaries. The records document technical services at the Yale University Library.
Academic libraries -- Administration; Technical services (Libraries); Yale University -- Administration; Yale University. Library
- Records, 1948-1977; Accession 1979-A-031
  Conditions Governing Access
  The materials are open for research.
  - Acquisitions Department, 1965-76,undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Acquisitions Department
    - Gifts and exchanges, 1950-75, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Policies, 1954-73, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Staff, 1966-76, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Subscriptions, centralization of, 1951-54, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - A.L.A. Conference, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - American National Standards Institute (ANSI), 1970-76, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Association of Research Libraries (ARL), 1967-76, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Automation Division, 1968-75, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Card catalogue, 1976-77, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Cataloging in Source, 1958-61 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Catalogue Department, cost, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Catalogue Department, staff, 1971-76, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Committee on American Library Resources on Southern Asia, 1962-64, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Conferences, Yale Staff Development Retreat, 1974 May 14-16 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - CONSER, 1974-76 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, miscellaneous, 1966-76 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Job descriptions, 1970, 1974, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Librarian's Conference, 1977-79 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Library assistants, 1970, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - L.C. Classification, Reclassification Report, 1969, statistics, etc., 1967, 1969, undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - L.C. MARC Report, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Library of Congress, Public Law 480, 1968-76, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Library of Congress, Public Law 480:
    - Annual Report, 1969-71 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Cataloging, 1962-64 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Cost, 1962-72 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Harvard, 1967-71 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - India, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - L.C. cards, 1969-74 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Pakistan, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Library Survey (Cresap, etc.) L. and B. classification, 1950, 1963, undated 1955, undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Medical Library Midrash, 1970-75 1965 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - National Serials Data Program, 1967-74 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - O.C.L.C., Advisory Committee on Cataloging, 1972-74, undated (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - O.C.L.C., Advisory Committee Serials, 1972-74, undated (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Orientation-Classification, J.E. Hitchcock, 1953-54, undated (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Paging, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Palmer Schreiber Library, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Professional Staff Association, 1975-77 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Rannit Committee, Personnel, 1969-70 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Selective Book Retirement Program Statistics, 1959-62 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Shuttle bus, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Staff News, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Systems Office, 1974-76 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Working Hours, Committee on, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Yale University, 1967-76 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Records, 1966-1978; Accession 1980-A-035
  - Kline Science Library Book Catalog, 1966 May (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Librarian's Annual Report, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Librarian's Annual Report, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Machine Aided Technical Processing System, 1972-1978 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - MATPS -Acquisitions, 1969-1978 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - MATPS -Development, 1969-1973 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - MATPS -Interstatus Flow, 1975-1977 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - MATPS -Processing Routine, etc., 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - MATPS -Processing Routines, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Near East Cataloging Unit, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - New England Library Information Network, 1976-1978 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - NELINET -Channel, 1974-1978 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - NELINET -Costs, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - OHIO College Library Center, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - OCLC -Cataloging, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - OCLC -Newsletter, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - OCLC -Serials, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Preservation and Preparations Dept., 1978 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Princeton University, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Serials Alerting Bulletin, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Serials Division, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Serials Task Force, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Southeast Asia Thai Cataloging, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Catalog Code Revision Committee Joint Steering Committee, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - CCRC Meetings, 1975-1977 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Resource and Technical Service Division/CCRC, 1974-1978 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - RTSD -CCRC/LC, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - RTSD -CCRC/Lim. 0-5, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - RTSD -CCRC/Lim. 6-10, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - RTSD -CCRC/Lim. 11-15, 1974-1976 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - RTSD -CCRC/Lim. 16-20, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - RTSD -CCRC/Lim. 21-25, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - RTSD -CCRC/Lim. 26-30, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - RTSD -CCRC/Lim. 31-35, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - RTSD -CCRC/Lim. 36-40, 1975 (summer) (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - RTSD -CCRC/Lim. 41, 1976 January-September (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - RTSD -CCRC/MRDF 1, 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - RTSD -CCRC M1-10, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Joint Steering Committee/CCRC1, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - JSC/CCRC (a), 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - JSC/ED-1, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - JSC/LC-1, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - JSC/M, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - JSC/RR, 1975 -1976 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - JSC/Sec. -1, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - JSC/UK-l, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - JSC, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - JSC-CCCl, 1975 December (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Team Ifl rules 1-5 kebabian and 17-18 (Entry gen.), 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Team 112 rule 6 (Entry Socials) Edgar, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Team /13 rules 7-13, 1975 March-April (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Team 118 rules 40-43 [Persons-general rules], 1975 June (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - ALA-LA-Agreement on Catalog Code Division (Box 8, Folder 53)
- Records, 1975-1983; Accession 1988-A-076
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2018
  - Chronological files, 1975-76 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Chronological files, 1977-79 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Annual report, 1982-83 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Organization change, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Statistics, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Annual repors statistics of University Libraries, 1976-1986; Accession 1988-A-096
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2021
  - 1976-81 (Box 1, Folder 1-6)
  - 1981-82 (Box 1, Folder 7-8)
  - 1982-84 (Box 2, Folder 9-13)
  - 1983-84 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - 1984-85 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - 1984-86 (Box 3, Folder 16-17)
  - 1985-86 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - 1977, 81, 82 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Records, 1944-1988; Accession 1989-A-061
  - Automation: Cataloging Work Sheets: Other Libraries, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Automation: Cataloging Work Sheet, 1965-68 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Broude Report, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Columbia University, 1970-80 (Box 1, Folder 4-5)
  - Automation: Columbia-Harvard-Yale Computer Project, 1964-71 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Cornell University, 1968-76 (Box 1, Folder 7-10)
  - Data Banks, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Descriptive Cataloguing Division: Ouput and Staff, 1979-80 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Forms, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Grossman Report, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Johns Hopkins University, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Linolian and Brothers in Unity, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Library of Congress --National Program for Acquisitions and Cataloging, 1973-77 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Library of Congress --Anglo-American Cataloging Rules, 1977-78 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Library of Congress, 1976-80 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Librarian's Conference Minutes, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Machine-Readable Technical Processing Services --Interstatus Flow, 1978-79 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Nelinet, 1979-80 (Box 1, Folder 23-25)
  - Nelinet --Technical Memoranda, 1977-79 (Box 1, Folder 26-27)
  - Foreign Government Publications, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - New York Public Library, 1971-78 (Box 1, Folder 29-31)
  - Ohio College Library Center --Advisory Committee on Technical Processing, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Preservation and Preparations Department, 1977-79 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Reclassification Division, 1978-80 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Reclassification Division--Output, 1979-81 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Reclassification Division--Staff, 1979-80 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Research Library Group, 1986-88 (Box 2, Folder 37-39)
  - Seeley Mudd Library, Including SML Moving Committee, 1979-82 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Serials Alerting Bulletin, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Stanford University, 1959-79 (Box 2, Folder 42-43)
  - Survey Annex Library, 1977-78 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Systems Office, 1977-79 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Technical Services, 1976-78 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Transfer, 1979-82 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Unions, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Administrative Computing at Yale University, 1982-84 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Acquisitions Annual Report, 1984-85 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Salaries--Confidential (Restricted until 1/1/2060), 1984 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Strike Contingency Plans, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Automation--Videodisks, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Ballots Newsletter, 1977-78 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Bowker Data Base, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Budget, 1978-79 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Collection Development, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Computer Center Library, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Association of Research Libraries--Task Force on Bibliographical Control, 1978-84 (Box 2, Folder 59-60)
  - Committee on Catalogue Continuation, 1982-83 (Box 2, Folder 61-63)
  - Committee on Catalogue Implementation, 1984-85 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Committee on the Future of the Card Catalogue --Subcommittee, 1978-83 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Committee on Scientific and Technical Information, undated (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - CRESAP Report, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Denver, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Harvard University--Ishimoto, 1971-78 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Harvard University, 1971-78 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Interim Catalogue Task Force, 1978-80 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Research Libraries Group:
    - Cataloging Statistics--Peter Graham, 1974-77 (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - Bibliographic Processes and Control: BIBPAC--Minutes, 1973-77 (Box 3, Folder 74-76)
    - Bibliographic Processes and Control: BIBPAC, 1977-80 (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - Ballots, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - Bibliographic Center, 1973-79 (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - Anglo-American Cataloging Rules II, 1976-77 (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - Graham, 1976-1978 (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - Executive Committee, 1974-79 (Box 3, Folder 82-83)
    - Library of Congress, 1974-80 (Box 3, Folder 84-86)
    - Plenary Meetings, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - Serials Coordinators, 1977-79 (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - Serials Program Manual, 1975-78 (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - Shaw, 1978-81 (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - Skipper, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Research Libraries Information Network--Use Cataloging, 1981-82 (Box 3, Folder 94-95)
  - Scandinavian Imprints, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Sterling Memorial Library, undated (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Technical Services Automation Council, 1979-82 (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Technical Services Annual Report Materials, 1976-77 (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Technical Services Annual Report, 1973-76 (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Technical Services, 1965-75 (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Conferences: American Library Association - Annual, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Conferences: Association of Research Libraries - Salt Lake City, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Hofsas, 1975-78 (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Conferences: American Library Association, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - Technical Services Memoranda, 1969-74 (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Technical Services Directors for Large Research Libraries, 1968-77 (Box 4, Folder 107-108)
  - Technical Services--Cost, 1973-76 (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Technical Services' Senior Staff Meetings: TSSSM, 1975-76 (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - Technical Services--Planning Documents, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - Union--Contract Negotiations, 1984-85 (Box 4, Folder 112-113)
  - Anglo-American Cataloging Rules 2, 1972-86 (Box 4, Folder 114-116)
  - Anglo-American Cataloging Rules 2--Yale-Implementation, 1978-79 (Box 4, Folder 117)
  - Anglo-American Cataloging Rules 2--Preconference, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 118)
  - Anglo-American Cataloging Rules 2--Impact on Catalogues, 1978-80 (Box 4, Folder 119-121)
  - Anglo-American Cataloging Rules 2--Serials, 1979-80 (Box 4, Folder 122)
  - Anglo-American Cataloging Rules 2--0ptions -Library of Congress, 1979-86 (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - Anglo-American Cataloging Rules 2--Library of Congress--Implementation, 1977-82 (Box 4, Folder 124-125)
  - Anglo-American Cataloging Rules 2 [General], 1978-83 (Box 4, Folder 126)
  - Anglo-American Cataloging Rules 2--Library of Congress--Freezing of Catalogues, 1977-80 (Box 4, Folder 127)
  - Authorship, 1976-78 (Box 4, Folder 128)
  - Authorship, Corporate, 1968-82 (Box 5, Folder 129)
  - Catalog Code Revision:
    - Cost of Changes at Library of Congress, 1960-61 (Box 5, Folder 130)
    - Institutions, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 131)
    - KASER (Association of Research Libraries), 1965 (Box 5, Folder 132)
    - Legal Materials, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 133)
    - Minutes, Agenda, 1957-65 (Box 5, Folder 134)
    - Objectives and Principles, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 135)
    - Oriental Names, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 136)
    - Liturgy and Ritual, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 137)
    - Serials: Miami, Stanford Papers, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 138)
    - Steering Committee--Reply to Dewton, 1961-62 (Box 5, Folder 139)
    - Subjects Replacing Form Headings, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 140)
    - Yale Catalog, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 141)
    - Steering Committee, 1957-65 (Box 5, Folder 142-143)
  - Institute on Catalog Code Revision--Montreal, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 144)
  - Hopkins, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 145)
  - Patron Survey of a University Library Catalog, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 146)
  - Catalog Code Revision Studies, [1960-61] (Box 5, Folder 147)
  - Catalog Code Revision: Bible Apocrypha, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 148)
  - Institute on Catalog Code Revision--Stanford, 1953-58 (Box 5, Folder 149)
  - Paris Principles, 1961-64 (Box 5, Folder 150)
  - Research Libraries Group--Organization (Rosenthal Report, etc.), 1972-73 (Box 5, Folder 151)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 152)
  - Outline of a Course in Cataloging, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 153)
- Administrative records, 1985-1993; Accession 1995-A-018
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2028
  - AACR 2 (Box 1)
  - ACADEMIC COMPUTING (Box 1)
  - ADVISORY COMMITTEE ON LIBRARY AUTOMATION (Box 1)
  - ADVISORY COMMITTEE ON LIBRARY POLICY (Box 1)
  - ARABIC AND ISLAMIC READING ROOM (Box 1)
  - ARABIC STUDIES PROPOSAL (Box 1)
  - ART and ARCIDTECTURE LIBRARY (Box 1)
  - ASBESTOS REMOVAL (Box 1)
  - ASSOCIATION OF RESEARCH LIBRARIES (ARL) (Box 1)
  - ASSOCIATION OF RESEARCH LIBRARIES - WORKING GROUP FOR TIMELY SERIALS (Box 1)
  - ARTRAN GRANT (Box 1)
  - AUCTION AND SALES CATALOGS (Box 1)
  - AUDIO VISUAL MATERIALS (Box 1)
  - AUTOMATION (Box 1)
  - AUTOMATION - COSTS (Box 1)
  - AUTOMATION - EQUIPMENT REPLACEMENT PLAN (Box 1)
  - BAC (Box 1)
  - BIBLIOFILE (Box 1)
  - BITNET (Box 1)
  - BUDGET - AUL PROJECT (Box 1)
  - BUDGET - CENTRAL - RESPONSffiILITY COSTS (Box 1)
  - BUOOET-CUTS (Box 1)
  - BUDGET - CUTS - COST REDUCTION QUESTIONNAIRE (Box 1)
  - BUOOET - DISCRETIONARY FUND (Box 1)
  - BUDGET FY 1986/1987 (Box 1)
  - BUDGET FY 1987/1988 (Box 1)
  - BUDGET FY 1988/1989 (Box 1)
  - BUDGET FY 1989/1990 (Box 1)
  - BUDGET FY 1990/1991 I (Box 1)
  - BUDGET FY 1990/1991 II (Box 1)
  - BUDGET FY 1991/1992 I (Box 1)
  - BUDGET FY 1991/1992 II (Box 1)
  - BUDGET FY 1991/1992 III (Box 1)
  - BUDGET FY 1992/1993 (Box 1)
  - BUDGET FY 1993/1994 (Box 1)
  - BUDGET-INDIRECT COSTS (Box 1)
  - BUDGET - INTEGRATED FINANCIAL PLAN I (Box 1)
  - BUDGET - INTEGRATED FINANCIAL PLAN II (Box 1)
  - BUDGET - LIBRARY INCOME (Box 1)
  - BUDGET - PRINCETON (Box 1)
  - BUDGET - REDUCTION PROJECT (Box 1)
  - BUDGET - REDUCTION PROJECT - TECHNICAL SERVICES (Box 1)
  - CAPITAL PLANNING (Box 1)
  - CARD CATALOGS - YALE (Box 1)
    - Authority Work (Box 1)
    - Closing (Box 1)
    - Filing (Box 1)
    - User Survey (Box 1)
  - CARLYLE (Box 1)
  - CATALOGING ASSISTANCE PROJECT (Box 1)
  - CATALOGING STANDARDS (Box 1)
  - CD MARC (Box 1)
  - CDS (Box 1)
  - CENTER FOR RESEARCH LIBRARIES (CRL) (Box 1)
  - CIRCULATION DEPARTMENT (Box 1)
  - CJK (Box 1)
  - COLLECTION DEVELOPMENT COUNCn.. (Box 1)
  - COLLECTION DEVELOPMENT POLICY (Box 1)
  - COLLEGE LmRARY TECHNOLOGY AND COOP PROGRAM (Box 1)
  - C0MUNICATIONS DEPARTMENT (Box 2)
  - CONSER I (Box 2)
  - CONSER II (Box 2)
  - CONSER III (Box 2)
    - Directory (Box 2)
    - Conser Executive Committee (Box 2)
    - Fall 1988 (Box 2)
    - FaIl 1990 (Box 2)
    - Microteehnology Task Force (Box 2)
    - Multiple Versions Task Force I (Box 2)
    - Multiple VersiQns Task Force II (Box 2)
    - Policy Committee Fall 1989 I (Box 2)
    - Policy Committee Fall 1989 II (Box 2)
    - Policy Committee Fall 1990 (Box 2)
    - Pricing (Box 2)
    - Retreat 1986 (Box 2)
  - CONSERVATION COMMITIEE (Box 2)
  - CONSORTIUM FOR LANGUAGE TEACHING AND LEARNING (Box 2)
  - COPYRIGHT (Box 2)
  - CLR (COUNCIL ON LIBRARY RESOURCES) (Box 2)
  - CUSTODIAL SERVICES (Box 2)
  - DANTE PROJECT (Box 2)
  - DATABASE MANAGEMENT DEPARTMENT (Box 2)
  - Annual Report (Box 2)
  - DEVELOPMENT OFFICE (Box 2)
  - DEZ (Box 2)
  - DRAMALIBRARY (Box 2)
  - EAST ASIAN COLLECTION (Box 2)
  - Hong Kong Project (Box 2)
  - Romanization (Box 2)
  - EBSCO (Box 2)
  - EDUCOM (Box 2)
  - ELECTRONIC MAIL (Box 2)
  - ENCYCLOPEDIA OF LIBRARY AND INFORMATION SCIENCE (Box 2)
  - ENDOWMENT FUNDS (Box 2)
  - EPH (Box 2)
  - EQUIPMENT (Box 2)
    - Acknowledgment (Box 2)
    - Equipment Request - FY 1986/87 (Box 2)
    - Equipment Request - FY 1987/88 (Box 2)
    - Equipment Request - FY 1988/89 (Box 2)
    - Equipment Request - FY 1989/90 (Box 2)
    - Equipment Request - FY 1990/91 (Box 2)
    - Equipment Request - FY 1991/92 (Box 2)
    - Equipment Request - FY 1992/93 (Box 2)
  - FAXON (Box 3)
  - FEES AND FINES (Box 3)
  - FIRE EVACUATION (Box 3)
  - FORESTRY LIBRARY (Box 3)
  - GAY AND LESBIAN STUDIES (Box 3)
  - GEACI (Box 3)
  - GEAC II (Box 3)
  - GOVERNMENT DOCUMENTS (Box 3)
  - GPO TAPES (Box 3)
  - GRANTS (Box 3)
  - HARRASSOWITZ (Box 3)
  - HEALTH AND SAFETY (Box 3)
  - HISTORICAL SOUND RECORDINGS (Box 3)
  - HUMANITIES COMPUTING ADVISORY COUNCIL (Box 3)
  - HYMGROUP (Box 3)
  - IAEMS (Box 3)
  - IBM-DOBIS (Box 3)
  - INFORMA (Box 3)
  - INNOVATIVE INTERFACES (Box 3)
  - INTEGRATED LIBRARY SYSTEM WORKSHOP (Box 3)
  - INSTRUCTIONAL TECHNOLOGY GROUP (Box 3)
  - INTELLECTUAL FREEDOM (Box 3)
  - INTERLIBRARY LOAN DISCUSSION GROUP (Box 3)
  - INTERNET (Box 3)
  - INTERNSHIPS (Box 3)
    - Administrative (Box 3)
    - Senior Fellows (Box 3)
    - Silverstein (Box 3)
    - Undergraduate (Box 3)
  - INVOICE PROCESSING (Box 3)
  - JOB AUDIT (Box 3)
  - JOB DESCRIPTIONSt GENERIC (Box 3)
  - LATIN AMERICAN COLLECTION (Box 3)
  - LAW LIBRARY (Box 3)
  - LEADERSHIP DEVELOPMENT PROGRAM (Box 3)
  - LEWIS WALPOLE LIBRARY (Box 3)
  - LIBRARY ACQUISITIONS SURVEY (Box 3)
  - LIBRARY COMMITTEE ON PROVISION OF ACCESS TO MACHINE READABLE DATA FILES (Box 3)
  - LIBRARY HOURS (Box 3)
  - LIBRARY OF CONGRESS (Box 3)
    - Copy Cataloging Seminar (Box 3)
    - Licensing (Box 3)
    - Network Advisory Committee (Box 3)
    - Remote Access (Box 3)
  - LIBRARY PLANNING AND BUDGET COMMITIEE (Box 3)
  - LIBRARY POLICY MANUAL (Box 3)
  - LINX (Box 3)
  - LISTSERV-YUL (Box 3)
  - LOCAL SYSTEMS (Box 3)
  - LSP (Box 3)
  - MAINFRAME DATABASE COMMITIEE (Box 3)
  - MAINFRAME DATABASE SYSTEMS (Box 3)
  - M and P JOB AUDIT (Box 3)
    - Appeals (Box 3)
  - M and P SALARY MERIT TASK FORCE (Box 3)
  - MANUSCRIPTS and ARCHIVES (Box 3)
  - MAPS (MID-ATLANTIC PRESERVATION SERVICE) (Box 3)
  - MATHEMATICS LIBRARY (Box 3)
  - MATPS (Box 3)
    - Description (Box 3)
  - MEDICAL LIBRARIAN SEARCH COMMITiEE (Box 4)
  - MEDICAL LIBRARY (Box 4)
    - Annual Report (Box 4)
    - Budget (Box 4)
    - Staffing (Box 4)
  - MEDLINE (Box 4)
  - MICROCOMPUTER ADVISORY BOARD (Box 4)
  - MICROCOMPUTING I (Box 4)
  - MICROCOMPUTING II (Box 4)
  - MICROFORMS - YALE (Box 4)
  - MICROSOFT (Box 4)
  - MPG (Box 4)
  - MRDF (Box 4)
  - MRDF - YALE (Box 4)
  - MUSIC LIBRARY (Box 4)
  - NACO (Box 4)
  - NAME-TITI..E CATALOG (Box 4)
  - NATIONAL REGISTER OF MICROFORM MASTERS (Box 4)
  - NCCP I (Box 4)
  - NCCP II (Box 4)
  - NCCPIII (Box 4)
    - Cataloging Simplification (Box 4)
    - Connections (Box 4)
    - Coordinated Cataloging (Box 4)
    - Cost Study (Box 4)
    - Record Contribution Options (Box 4)
  - NETWORK MANAGEloJENT BOARD (Box 4)
  - NETWORKING (Box 4)
    - Committee (Box 4)
    - Electronic Mail (Box 4)
    - Lan (Box 4)
  - NEW ENGLAND ACRL (Box 4)
  - NEWSPAPERS (Box 4)
  - NEXT (Box 4)
  - NOTIS (Box 4)
    - Acquisitions (Box 4)
      - Alert (Box 4)
      - Audit (Box 4)
      - Deposit Account (Box 4)
      - End of Fiscal Year (Box 4)
      - Invoice Processing (Box 4)
      - Support Group (Box 4)
      - Training (Box 4)
      - Walker System (Box 4)
      - Working Group (Box 4)
    - African Collection (Box 4)
    - AITF (Box 4)
    - NOTISAMC (Box 4)
    - Art and Architecture Library (Box 4)
    - Authority Control (Box 4)
    - Automation Documents (Box 4)
    - Automation Principles (Box 4)
    - Backup and Recovery (Box 4)
    - Beinecke Library (Box 4)
    - Brigham Young (Box 4)
    - Budget (Box 4)
      - Backup (Box 4)
      - Budget Committee Presentation (Box 5)
      - Budget Committee Proposal (Box 5)
      - Budget Committee Proposal- Original (Box 5)
      - Cand IS (Box 5)
      - Costs - June (Box 5)
      - Costs - October (Box 5)
      - Distributing Costs to Cost Centers (Box 5)
      - FY 88/89 (Box 5)
      - Grant Proposals (Box 5)
      - Haroware (Box 5)
      - Review 2/89 (Box 5)
      - Review 2/90 (Box 5)
      - Review 2/91 (Box 5)
    - Cataloging (Box 5)
    - Cataloging Working Group (Box 5)
    - CCL (Box 5)
    - Circulation (Box 5)
    - Client Server (Box 5)
    - College Libraries (Box 5)
    - Communication (Box 5)
    - Contract (Box 5)
    - Cornell (Box 5)